欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内 字幕广告招租 商业合作Q:1585235535
不好意思 我的天
Whoa, sorry about that. Oh, my God.
老兄 你干什么
Whoa, man, what are you doing?
喂 放开他
Hey! Get off of him!
-不  -拜托 老兄
- No. - Hey, come on, guy.
我没有义务把她的存在告诉你
I didn't have to tell you about her,
但我还是坦白了 因为这是唯一的解决办法
but I came clean because that's the only way through this.
我们必须要对彼此坦诚
We have to be honest with each other,
即便是那些困难的事情
even about the hard stuff.
困难就在于你对别人有感觉
The hard stuff is you having feelings for somebody else.
咱们聊聊这件事
Let's talk about that.
我不是有意的
I didn't mean for it to happen.
我每天跟她一起工作
I work with her every day.
我们一起吃午饭
We have lunch together.
我会跟她说我不得不去办的杂事
I tell her about the errands I have to run,
跟她说孩子们是怎么把我累垮的
how- - how the kids run me ragged,
都是那些组成生活的普通细节
the mundane details that make a life.
这是我们的生活 这些事情
A life we share. You should have been
你应该是跟我说的
talking to me about this stuff.
你在家的话 当然可以啊
When you're around, sure.
我们在一起很好
We're good together.
当我们在一起的时候
I mean, when we are together,
确实很好
it's good.
我也觉得
I agree.
但我们要怎么度过这一切
But how are we gonna get through this?
我不知道
I don't know.
等一下 抱歉
One second. One sec. Sorry.
V I
我就是这个意思
This is exactly what I mean.
是她上司推荐了你之后
She's the one who convinced me to try therapy
她说服我来尝试一下治疗的
after her boss recommended you.
我没办法让她专注于我们的当下
I can never get her to stay present.
我理解
I understand.
先努力耐心一点 我们慢慢解决这个问题
Just try to be patient, and we will work on that.
抱歉 我得走了
I'm sorry, I have to go.
谢里尔 我们在正在进行很重要的
Sheryll, we're in the middle of something important-
托宾大学发生枪击案 枪手在逃
There is an active shooter at Tobin University.
我还能怎么办
What am I supposed to do?
你不是局里唯一一个探员
You're not the only agent they can call.
我必须得走了 小夏
I have to go, Char.
我的团队需要我 好吗
My team needs me, all right?
我们不是一个团队吗
I thought we were a team.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
找枪手对质的人是个在休假的警察
The guy who confronted the shooter was an off- duty cop.
另一个被害人呢
What about the other victim?
是洒吧安保人员 叫卡斯帕·琼斯
Bouncer named Casper Jones,
大四学生 在这里工作了两年
senior, worked here for two years.
目击者说枪手跑了出去
Witnesses said the shooter ran outside,
进了校园
went onto campus.
现在这小孩带着枪
We got a kid with a gun
往有一万名学生的校园里逃跑
running loose on a campus of 10, 000 students.
怪不得找我们来帮忙了
No wonder they asked for our help.
监控拍到了枪击发生的过程 但是画质很差
There is footage of the shooting, but it was grainy.
枪手是黑人男性 穿着黄色的托宾大学帽衫
The shooter is a Black male wearing a yellow Tobin hoodie.
可能是个遇到了麻烦的学生 所以他才跑进了校园
Could be a troubled student, that's why he ran on campus.
或许吧 但目前为止 没有学生认识他
Maybe, but so far, none of the kids recognize him.
校园各处都有很多
We're getting slammed with reports of gunshots
枪击事件的报告出现
on opposite sides of the campus- -
科技楼 学生工会 体育中心
science building, student union, the athletic center.
家长也在打电话来
Parents are also calling.
他们收到了封锁中的孩子们的短信
They're getting texts from their kids in lockdown.
有些人说他们在大一宿舍里听到了枪声
Some are saying they heard gunshots at a freshman dorm.
人们恐慌担心有多个枪手
Yeah, it's common for people to panic
这是很正常的 但这次很有可能
about multiple shooters, but it's more than likely
只有一个嫌犯
a sole perpetrator.
直到发现不止一个 就像科伦拜中学校园枪击案一样
Until it's not, like Columbine.
继续查找枪手的身份
Keep trying to ID the gunman.
我们已经完成了对科技楼大半的排查
We're halfway through clearing the science building.
应急响应小组正在准备攻入学生工会
ESU's prepping to breach the student union.
我们也正在派警官到各个宿舍
We're sending officers into the dorms now.
巴恩斯 跟我来
Barnes, with me.
雷和妮娜你们去宿舍 出发吧
Ray, Nina, take the dorm. Let's roll.
我觉得我们应该进去
I think we should get inside.
现在就是坐以待毙
We're sitting ducks.
那是宿舍
It's a dorm.
你需要本科生的证件才能刷卡进去
You need an undergrad ID to swipe in.
我的卡没用
My ID won't work.
我刚才给妈发了短信
I texted Mom earlier.
我爱你
I love you.
我不会让你出事的
I won't let anything happen to you.
2020年抗议发生的时候
I was studying abroad in Cairo
我在开罗留学
when the 2020 protests happened.
那太疯狂了 我父母都快怕死了
It was insane, and my parents were freaking out,
但现在是我这辈子最害怕的一刻
but this is the most scared I've ever been.
你们看 警察来了
Look, the cops are coming.
-我们会没事的 亲爱的  -好
We're gonna be okay, honey. - Okay.
-我们走  -好
Let's go. All right.
-走  -我们走
Come on. Let's go.
别
Don't.
不 求你了 不要
No, please, please, please.
救命 他在这里
Help! He's over herel
我 我的天
Oh, my- oh, my Godl
不不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no.
-求你了 不要  -我不想伤害你们
Please, no, no. - I don't want to hurt you.
-有人受伤  -我看到了
Man down. Yeah, see him.
好 他还有呼吸
Okay, he's still breathing.
各位 立刻派急救人员到纽伯里宿舍门口
Guys, we need a medic outside of Newbury Dorm.
一名男性受枪伤
We have a male with a gunshot wound.
你们有受伤吗
Are either of you hurt?
-没有  -他往那边去了
No. - He went that way.
No. He went that way.
好 听着 他们会照顾好你的
AlI right, look, these guys will take care of. you.
好吗 我们走
AII right? Come on.
雷米 我们正在追缉枪手
Remy, we're in pursuit.
在校园内往东走
Heading east on campus.
有第二名枪手的迹象吗
Any sign of a second shooter?
没有 你看
No. Hey, look.
他可能知道被他们看到了
He could have ditched it knowing that they got
-所以扔了黄色帽衫  -上报上去
a good look at him. Call it in.
我们得继续走 我往这边去
We gotta keep moving. I'll go this way.
联调局
FBI.
手举起来
Keep your hands in the air.
-去搜身  -这就去
Go search him. - On it.
你有看到枪手 或者听到什么声音吗
You seen the shooter or heard anything?
我不知道 我们收到短信警报叫我们原地别动
I don't know, we got a text alert to stay put,
可然后又收到一条叫我们撤离的
but then we got another text saying to evacuate.
好 你原地别动 别起身
Okay. Stay here and lay low.
-你看好他  -收到
You watch him. - Roger.
好了 所有人都出去
AlI right, everybody out!
走 走 走 快 快 快
Out, out, out! Move, move, move, movel
排队 排队
Line up. Line up.
搜他们身
Search'em.
警方正在破开上锁的教室门
The police are breaking down the locked classrooms
帮忙疏散大楼内人群
to help evacuate the building.
你们有谁看到枪手了呜
Did any of you see the shooter?
好了 把他们带到安全的地方
AlI right, bring them to safety.
校园内有枪手在逃
Got an active shooter!
请所有人找地方躲避 等待警情解除
Everybody shelter in place until you hear otherwisel
走 快走
Movel Go!
走啊
Go!
你在干什么啊
What are you doing?
这里应该要封锁起来的好吗
Look, this area should have been locked down, right?
不允许任何人进出
Nobody in or out.
妮娜 你那边有发现吗
Nina, you got anything?
没有 什么都没有
No, nothing.
我这里也什么都没有
Look, there's nothing here.
天知道他去了哪里
He could be anywhere.
-最新情况如何  -已确保校园安全
- What's the latest? - Campus is secure.
他们设立了统一中心
They set up a reunification center
给学生和家属
for the students and their families.
但哈娜有发现
Hana's got something, though.
是的 当时狼穴酒吧人满为患
Yeah, so the Wolf Den was packed.
正好是打折时间 但是根据社交媒体
It was happy hour. But with tags
上面的表情和地理定位
and geolocation sharing from social media
再加上兄弟会办的野格炸弹挑战
and the Delta Zeta Nu's Jagerbomb Challenge,
所以我找到了枪手的正脸照片
I was able to get a clear shot of our shooter.
曼尼·海耶斯曼 23岁
Manny Hayesman 23 years old.
Manny Hayesman, 23 years old.
他最后登记的地址是在康涅狄格州的东哈特福德
His last- known is in East Hartford, Connecticut,
他和他爸同住
where he lives with his dad.
奇怪的是 我还真听说过这人
Weirdly, I've actually heard of this guy.
-此话怎讲  -我同父异母的弟弟乔治
- How come? - So my half brother George
在曼尼被他最爱的澳大利亚男子篮球联赛
wouldn't shut up when he got signed for the NBL in Australia
球队签下之后 一直在跟我唠叨曼尼的事
for playing for one of his favorite teams.
他是个篮球运动员吗
He's a basketball player?
是的 他是联赛中
Yeah, he played for one of the only
少数几支新西兰球队的球员
New Zealand teams in the league.
所以他是怎么从
Okay, so how does this guy go
在新西兰打篮球进化成
from shooting hoops in New Zealand
到皇后区的大学来枪击的呢
to shooting up a school in Queens?
我不知道 他不是
I don't know. He's not listed
托宾大学的学生 但是他确实有前科
as a student at Tobin, but he does have a prior,
两个月前在东哈特福德
a misdemeanor drug possession
一次持毒的轻罪
two months ago in East Hartford.
好 我刚问过校警
Okay, I just spoke to Campus PD.
他们说狼穴酒吧是学生之间
They said that the Wolf Den is a known hangout
著名的毒品购买胜地
where students go to buy drugs.
看来这卖的不是安非他命和阿得拉之类的小玩意儿吧
I take it we're not talking speed and Adderall.
摇头丸 兴奋剂 可卡因
More like Molly, ecstasy, coke.
好 所以这可能是毒品交易出了问题
Okay, so maybe this is a drug deal gone wrong.
也就是说不是校园枪击
So not a school shooting,
只是失控了而已
something that spiraled out of control.
说得通 我讯问的那个服务生说
Which tracks. The waitress I spoke to said
曼尼是在那个休假的警察冲向他之后
that Manny didn't start firing until after
才开始开枪的
the off- duty cop charged at him.
好 我们分头行动
AII right, let's split up.
你们去东哈特福德警局
You two take East Hartford PD,
弄清楚他们都知道些什么
find out what they know about this guy.
我和哈娜去找曼尼的父亲
Hana and I will go see Manny's dad.
对他发布全境通告
Get a BOLO out on this dude.
确保民众知道不能接近他
Make sure the public knows not to approach.
他持有武器 并且非常危险
He's armed and extremely dangerous.
显然他一点都不怕对警察
Obviously not afraid to shoot at cops
和无辜路人开枪
and innocent bystanders.
希望你们不会介意 我需要吃安神药
I hope you don't mind. I need this for my nerves.
没事
Not at all.
你知道曼尼有枪吗
Did you know Manny had a gun?
我不知道
No, I didn't.
我也不知道他那枪是哪儿来的
And I don't know where he'd get one, either.
那他的朋友们呢
What about his friends?
他没有朋友
He doesn't have any,
反正我是不知道有
at least that I know about.
曼尼的卧室里没什么东西啊
Manny doesn't keep much in his bedroom.
他最近都不怎么回家
He hardly comes around these days,
回来也只是拿点衣服或者扫荡冰箱
only to grab some clothes or raid the fridge.
他最近都跟谁一起混
Who's he hanging out with these days?
我也想知道
I wish I knew.
我想的可太多了
I wish a lot of things.
曼尼的目标是美国职业篮球联赛
Manny had his eyes set on the NBA,
几千万的高额合同
hundred- million- dollar contract,
在迈阿密买高级公寓
you know, mansion in Miami.
那他的NBA梦是怎么了
What happened to the big NBA dream?
他没坚持下去
Manny didn't stick with it long enough to find out.
他天赋是有的 但没耐性
What that boy had in talent he lacked in resilience.
一点点小挫折
Just the smallest setback,
他就会觉得全世界都晚了
and he would think the world was over.
什么样的挫折
What kind of setbacks?
受到中央堪萨斯大学的招募
Getting recruited by Central Kansas University
本该是他开启旅程的门票
was supposed to be his ticket.
他原本拿到了全额的邀约
He had an offer with a full ride.
但是他们在最后一刻撤回了
But they pulled it at the last minute.
他们有解释为什么吗
Did they ever say why?
他们没说 但我告诉他
They never said, but what I told him,
让他去读社区大学
just go to community college.
努力提高成绩 之后再想办法转过去
You know, get your grades up, try to transfer in later.
但他眼里只有钱
But all he could see was dollar signs.
所以他决定就这样直接去打职业
So he decided to go pro just like that.
我弟弟是他在新西兰时的球迷
My brother was a big fan when he played in New Zealand.
是啊
Yeah.
我也希望那能成为他的新开始
Yeah, I'd hoped that would be a fresh start.
也确实是成了 直到他在练习时伤了膝盖
And it was, until he blew his knee out in practice.
是这样的 对曼尼来说 篮球就是一切
See, with Manny, it's either basketball or bust.
他从新西兰回来之后
When he got back from New Zealand,
我根本无法和他对话
I couldn't reach him.
我
I- -
你儿子现在在逃
Your son's on the run now.
我相信他肯定非常害怕
And I'm sure he's very scared.
你知道他可能会向谁求助吗
Can you think of anyone he might go to for help?
或许前女友之类的
Maybe an old girlfriend.
唯一一个能说动他的就是东哈特福德这里
The only person who ever had his ear
沃尔福德高中他当时的教练
was his coach at Walford High here in East Hartford,
山姆·内森
Sam Nathan.
拜托
Come on.
什么
What?
你要这么耍我吗
You gonna play me like that?
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
该死
Damn it.
嗨 兄弟
Hey, yo, my man.
怎么了
What?
车钥匙给我
Give me your keys.
-什么  -立刻把车钥匙给我
What? - Give me your keys right now.
那你自己拿去啊
Go and get'em.
-好 好  -钥匙给我
Yeah. Yeah. Give me the keys.
给
Here.
还有你的钱包
Your wallet too.
-对  -你要什么都拿去
Yeah. - Take whatever you want.
-对  -都拿去
- Yeah. - Whatever you want.
我看到新闻的时候 简直不敢相信
I, uh, couldn't believe it when I saw the news.
我很久没有见过曼尼了
I haven't seen Manny in a long time.
但这 这太令人绝望了
But it's just- just devastating.
你教了他几年
You coached him for a number of years.
他有过暴力行为吗
Was he ever violent?
他是挺急躁的
He was a hothead.
但你知道的 那个年纪的男孩子
Boys that age, you know,
比赛的时候一上头 荷尔蒙就失控
their hormones running wild in the heat of the game.
他父亲说你是唯一一个
His father said that you're the only person
能说通他的
he would listen to.
曼尼是个很优秀的球员
Manny was a hell of a player.
本质不是个坏孩子 只是态度太差
Not a bad kid at heart, just had a horrible attitude.
怎么个差法
Horrible in what way?
他总是觉得自己知道怎么做才最好
He always thought he knew what was best,
忘记了篮球是团队运动
forgot it was a team sport.
他从新西兰回来已经快一年了
He's been back from New Zealand about a year now,
但他不怎么在家里待着
but he doesn't spend much time at home.
你知道他平时都在哪里吗
Where would he hang out?
我完全不知道
I have no idea.
我们没有保持联系
We didn't keep in touch,
这还挺让我伤心的
you know, and it hurts.
毕竟我们在一起那么长时间 是吧
All those hours together, you know?
我手下的球员对我来说就像家人一样
I'm like family with my players.
你知道中央堪萨斯大学
Do you have any idea why Central Kansas
为什么撤回了对曼尼的邀约吗
pulled Manny's offer?
我不是说了吗 他脾气太差
Like I said, horrible attitude.
他们可能回看了比赛录像
They probably looked at the tape again
发现他在场上失控太多次了
and saw too many blowups on the court.
这种事你在高中要逃掉是可以的
I mean, you can get away with that stuff in high school,
尤其是作为明星球员
especially if you're the star player.
但是大学里他们不会忍你的臭脾气
But in college, they won't put up with that crap.
你的职业生涯真是精彩啊
You've had one hell of a career.
是啊 我运气很好
Yeah, I've, uh- - I've been blessed.
不过说真的 胜利不会一直伴随着你
Honestly, though, it's not the wins that stay with you,
更重要的是看到那些孩子去做更大 更好的事情
it's seeing my boys go on to do bigger and better things.
曼尼真的很有潜力
Manny had so much potential.
所以 所以我才会觉得这么遗憾
That's- - that's why it's a damn shame.
谢谢你抽时间出来
Thanks for your time.
谢了
Thanks.
是 我在曼尼初中的时候就认识他了
Yeah, no, I've known Manny since he was in middle school.
我看档案里没有少年犯记录啊
Oh, there's no juvie record on file.
我认识他是因为他是那个八年级
I knew him because he was the eighth grader
就破了篮球州记录的选手
breaking state records on the basketball court.
所以突然之间 这个好学生
So all of a sudden, this student who's on
怎么会被抓到持毒呢
the straight and narrow gets busted for possession?
当时纽约警局对皇后区一个贩毒组织的调查
Well, Manny's name came up in an NYPD investigation
牵扯到了曼尼
of a drug ring in Queens.
其中一个毒贩指认曼尼 说他供应大麻
One of the dealers fingered Manny as a weed supplier,
就小镇上的那种
just small- town stuff.
听着 我了解曼尼
Listen, uh, I- I know Manny,
他不是什么硬核黑帮成员
and he wasn't some hard gangbanger.
纽约警局联系我们的时候 我没法无视这件事 但
When the NYPD called us, I couldn't ignore it, but, um-
你觉得他很可惜 所以把罪名
You felt bad for him and downgraded the charge
从贩毒减到持毒了 是吗
from distribution to possession?
我当时觉得这孩子配得上一个
I thought the kid deserved a chance to get back up
改过自新的机会 但如果我觉得他可能会有暴力行为
on his feet, but I never would have done it
我是绝对不会那么做的
if I thought he might become violent.
是谁向纽约警局指认了曼尼
Who gave the NYPD Manny's name?
科迪·本森 是个皇后区的酒保
Uh, Cody Benson. He's a bartender from Queens.
什么酒吧
What bar?
狼穴酒吧
The Wolf Den.
好 谢谢你的帮助
AlI right, thanks for your help.
曼尼已经是我的过去了
Manny is in my rearview mirror.
我不想聊他的事情
I don't wanna talk about him.
我的印度教宗教教师说我需要专注当下
My swami says I gotta stay centered on my present.
好极了 那当下
Great, well, right now in the present,
我们就在问你曼尼的事情
we're asking you about Manny.
所以你们是在你在狼穴酒吧工作期间认识的吗
So did you two meet while you were working at the Wolf Den?
是 但我几个月前就辞职了
Yeah. But I quit months ago.
你是辞职 还是因为被抓到
You quit, or you got fired
向学生贩毒 所以被开除了啊
after getting busted for dealing to students?
你们早知道的话
If you already know,
为什么非得提起这些负能量呢
why do we have to dredge up all this bad juju?
听着 曼尼是会给我大麻
Look, Manny would hook me up with weed,
但量不大 频率也不高
but not a lot and not often.
所以你觉得曼尼今天会不会是来追杀你的
So do you think Manny was after you today
因为他知道你出卖了他
because he knows you sold him out?
是我律师逼我的 为了避免坐牢
My lawyer made me. To avoid jail time.
我觉得曼尼应该不在乎是谁让你这么干的
Well, I doubt Manny cares who told you to do it.
我们派个探员在这栋楼外面
Why don't we post an agent
以防万一吧
outside your building just in case?
我不需要保姆
I don't need a babysitter.
曼尼是个衰人
Manny's a loser.
他根本没那个胆子来对我下手的
He doesn't have the guts to come after me.
他现在肯定不知道躲在哪儿怕得要死呢
He's probably hiding somewhere, scared out of his mind.
你所说的这个衰人
Well, that loser you were talking about
不到一小时前刚在离这里两英里的地方
just carjacked a blue Chrysler two miles from here
劫了一辆蓝色克莱斯勒
less than an hour ago.
车主现在在牙买加医院 情况危重
Driver's in Jamaica Medical in critical condition.
你的宗教教师还觉得
Hmm. Does your swami still think
我们应该取消你的警方保护吗
we should call off the police protection?
不
Uh, no.
他不会介意的
He'll be cool with it.
好
Okay.
嗨 彼得
Hey, Pete.
还记得我吗
Remember me?
我们应该没见过吧
Uh, I don't think we've met.
不 我们见过
Nah, we met before- -
早啊 彼得
Morning, Pete.
明天晚上你和安娜会过来打牌的吧
You and Anna are coming over for game night tomorrow, right?
让她别多管闲事
Tell her to mind her damn business.
赶紧的
Do it now.
玛丽我不认识这个男人
Uh, Mary, I don't know this man.
你能帮我个忙 报警吗 就现在
Can you do me a favor and call 911- - now?
-我的天  -上车
- Oh, my God! - Get in the car!
-走 走啊  -彼得
Go, go! - Petel
给我上车
Get in the car.
赶紧给我回家
Get in the house now!
彼得是我丈夫 我当时在上瑜伽课
Pete's my husband. I was at yoga class,
但玛丽一打电话我就回来了
but I came home as soon as Mary called.
这是你看到的那个人吗
Is this the guy you saw?
从蓝色克莱斯勒上下来的
Got out of the blue Chrysler?
是啊
Yes.
怎么会这样呢
I mean, how does this happen?
这里可是格林威治啊
This is Greenwich, for God's sakes.
我检查过车了 被害人的钱包被偷了
I checked the car. The victim's wallet was stolen.
现金和信用卡都不见了
Cash and credit cards are missing.
等一下 这是新闻上那个人吗
Wait a second. Was that the guy from the news?
昨天在纽约的大学里引发枪击案的
The one that shot up the college in New York yesterday?
对 是曼尼·海耶斯曼
Yeah, it's Manny Hayesman.
23岁 是个来自东哈特福德的篮球运动员
23- year- old basketball player from East Hartford.
篮球
Basketball.
我丈夫是个体育经纪人
My husband is a sports agent.
他认识曼尼吗
Does he know Manny?
我不知道 他有很多客户
I don't know. He has lots of clients,
但我从来没听他提过这个名字
but I haven't heard him mention that name before.
我的天
Oh, my God.
这人手里真有枪吗
This guy actually has a gun?
李太太 我们会找到彼得的 好吗 我保证
Ms. Lee, we will find Pete. All right, I promise.
我们需要你丈夫的客户名单
We need to see a list of your husband's clients.
他在附近有办公室吗
Does he have an office nearby?
有 周六是关门的
Yes. It's closed Saturdays,
但我可以打给他的助手亨特
but I can call Hunter. That's his assistant.
-让他去那边等你们  -好极了
He can meet you there. - Great.
麻烦你把地址写下来
Uh, if you can just write the address in there
然后打个电话
and then make that call.
好 谢谢你
Okay. Thank you.
我的天
Oh, my God.
我只想聊聊 好吗
I just want to talk, a'ight?
好 好
Yeah. Yeah.
你真的不记得我了吗
You really don't remember me, huh?
你来看过我比赛
You came to see one of my games,
还跟我聊过两句
you talked to me after.
我每天都要见很多球员
I met tons of prospects every day- -
你他妈都请我去你办公室了
You had me to your damn office.
你和你老板伊莱 跟我说了一堆谎言
You and your boss Eli fed me a bunch of lines
说什么会照顾好我
about taking care of me.
但是当中央堪萨斯大学撤回邀约的时候
But when Central Kansas pulled my offer,
你们就跑了
you bailed!
-曼尼  -是啊
- Manny. Mm- hmm.
曼尼·海耶斯曼
Manny Hayesman.
是 但我们 我们从未签过合同啊
Well, yeah, but we- - we never made a deal,
口头的 书面的都没有
orally or in writing- -
老兄 别跟我扯什么狗屁法律
Man, don't give me that legal BS.
你保证过 你会永远支持我的
You promised that you'd always have my back.
然后你就把我像垃圾一样扔了
But then you threw me away like a piece of trash.
这不是针对你
It wasn't personal.
代理一个没有队伍要的运动员是没有意义的
There's no point in repping an athlete without a team.
其他经纪人肯定也这么跟你说过吧
I'm sure other agents told you that.
我没有什么经纪人
I didn't have no agent.
我都指望你了
I was counting on you.
所以一次不走运 我对你来说就是个死人了 是吗
So one strike of bad luck, and I'm dead to you, huh?
你就是这么做事的吗
Is that how this goes?
你骗我 说会照顾我
You lied about taking care of me,
说会为我的职业生涯打算
about looking out for my career.
曼尼 对不起 真的
Manny, I'm sorry, I am.
但这一行生意就是这样的
But that's the way the business works.
那我们就聊聊生意
So let's get to business then.
这些都是彼得现在的客户
These are all of Peter's active clients.
我从来没听说过曼尼·海耶斯曼
I've never heard of Manny Hayesman,
但我 我查一下
but I'm- - I'm searching.
抱歉 没有结果
Sorry, no results found.
那老客户呢
What about old clients?
老客户不会在系统里
They wouldn't be in the system.
-这是沃尔特·费尔顿吗  -是啊
- Is this is Walt Felton? - Yeah.
是的 我们代表他签了联赛球队的合同
Yeah, we rep him for NIL.
这是我们签合同当晚的照片
That's the night we signed his deal.
他不肯点雪茄
Um, he wouldn't light his cigar,
彼得觉得那很好笑
and Peter thought it was hilarious.
沃尔特·费尔顿是谁
Who's Walt Felton?
是个篮球运动员
He's a basketball player.
去年高中选秀前五名
Top five recruit out of high school last year.
他还是个超级网红
He's also a huge influencer.
在网上有大概一千万粉丝
Has, like, 10 million followers online
他是去念杜克大学了 对吧
He goes to Duke, right?
等门户网站开了就会过去
He will when the portal opens.
彼得想先在纽约这里宣传他的品牌
Peter wanted to platform his brand here in New York first.
所以现在他是皇后区托宾大学的大一学生
So right now, he's a freshman at Tobin in Queens.
等等 昨天托宾的枪击案 就是曼尼干的吗
Wait, is- is Manny the one who shot up Tobin yesterday?
是他绑架了我老板吗
That's who kidnapped my boss?
是 听着 这可能是个巧合
Yeah. Look, it may be a coincidence
但有任何联系 我们都需要追查
but any connection is something that we need to follow.
雷 沃尔特昨天下午3点半在社交媒体上发帖
Ray, Walt posted on socials at 3: 30 yesterday.
今晚狼穴酒吧见
"Meetup at the Wolf Den tonight.
分区决赛前的狂欢 #冲啊狼队
Pregame hype for conference finals. #GoWolves. "
所以曼尼知道他会过去
So Manny knew he was gonna be there.
你们觉得他的目标是沃尔特吗
You think he was going after Walt?
你有这人的地址吗
Look, do you have an address on this guy?
-我们得和他聊聊  -有
We need to talk to him. - Yeah.
有 在曼哈顿
Yeah, it's in Manhattan.
我们一直有给他寄东西
We send him stuff all the time.
所以你昨晚没有去狼穴酒吧吗
So you weren't at the Wolf Den last night?
没有 我发了那篇帖子
No, ma'am. I posted that on my story
是为了让粉丝们兴奋起来 但我本来就不打算去
to get the fans excited, but I was never gonna go.
首发球员都没去
None of the starters were there.
我们想专心比赛
We were trying to focus.
所以你不认识曼尼·海耶斯曼
So you don't know Manny Hayesman?
不认识
No.
而且他为什么要绑架彼得呢
And why would he want to take Pete?
这就是我们想查清楚的
That's what we're trying to figure out.
我们调查了彼得的客户 你是唯一一个
We went through Pete's clients, and you're the only one
和曼尼还有狼穴酒吧有联系的人
with a connection to Manny and the Wolf Den.
因为他是我的粉丝吗
Because he follows me online?
我不是故意想显得讨人嫌 但我有很多很多粉丝
Well, not to be a jerk, but I have tons of followers,
绝大部分我都不认识
and I don't know 95%of them.
他也是打篮球的
He also plays basketball.
原本他是要去中央堪萨斯大学打球的
He had a full ride for Central Kansas,
而且他也在新西兰
and he also played pro in New Zealand
打过几年职业联赛
for a couple of years.
靠 我 没听过这人
Dang, I...never heard of him.
好 那你最后一次和彼得对话是什么时候
Okay. When is the last time you spoke with Pete?
我和彼得其实不太聊
Me and Pete don t really talk much.
我有个业务经理负责联赛的事情
I have a business manager that handles all the NIL stuff.
彼得会在比赛前后给我发短信
Pete will text me before or after a game,
但基本也就这样了
but that's about it.
我真的觉得他很可惜
You know, I feel terrible for him,
我也很想帮忙
and I really wish that I could help,
但我不知道还能和你们说什么了
but I just don't know what else I can tell you guys.
好
Okay.
嗨 迪 你等我一下行吗
Hey, D. Look, can you give me a second?
过去那边
You can go right over there.
那是我私教
That's the personal trainer.
为了今晚的比赛 我得做点理疗
I gotta do some physio for the game tonight.
都出了这么大的事了 他们不推迟比赛吗
They're not postponing it in light of what happened?
不 而且体育指导主任觉得
Nah, the AD think it'll be
这能向学生们展示出团结的一面
a good show of solidarity for the students.
而且学校也不会亏钱
And the school won't lose money.
我相信这也是部分原因
Well, I'm sure that's part of it,
但是我们队里也投了票 我们都想比赛
but the team voted, and we want to play.
好 你现在行动有警方保护吗
Okay, do you travel with a police escort?
-有  -很好
Yes, ma'am. - Good.
我们不确定曼尼的下一步行动会是什么
We're not sure what Manny's next move is,
所以记得时刻保持警惕 还有如果想起什么
so keep your eyes out, and you let us know
和彼得有关的事情 给我们打电话 好吗
if you think of anything when it comes to Pete, okay?
好
Okay.
好 谢谢你
AlI right, thank you.
拿最大额 快点
Take out the max. Hurry up.
我 我从来不带现金的
Okay, I- I never carry cash.
我不知道密码对不对
I don't know if I have the right PIN.
-赶紧取钱  -好好好
- Just do it. - Okay. okay.
等一下 等一下 让我想想
Uh, uh, w- wait, wait, wait. Let me think.
让我想想
Let me think. Um, um...
有了 有了 有了
I got it, I got it, I got it.
等等 这张卡是我老婆用的
Wait, my wife is the one
可能她改了密码
that uses this card. Maybe she changed the PIN.
-你故意搞事儿是吧  -不 我没有
- You messing up on purpose? - No, no.
该死的
Ugh, damn it!
求你了 如果 如果你要的是钱
Please, please, if- - if it's money you want,
那我可以另想办法的
I'll figure out another way.
我 天
I- - oh, God.
你没机会了
You missed your shot.
你没有价值 所以对我来说你就是个死人了
You got nothing to offer, so you're dead to me.
只是生意而已 对吧
It's just business, right? Hmm?
不 等等 求你了 不要伤害我 好吗
No, no, wait, please, please don't hurt me, okay?
那不是我决定的 我从来没想过
It wasn't my decision. I never meant
要抛弃你 但我没得选
to turn my back on you, but I had no choice.
是伊莱 伊莱 是他负责的
It was Eli. Eli, he was the one in charge.
当时我只是个刚入行的经纪人 所以当警察过来
I was just a junior agent. And when the cop came
告诉我们你所牵扯的事情之后
and told us what you were involved in,
伊莱就说我们必须得抛掉你
Eli said we had to drop you.
-机构本身是同意  -等下等下
The agency was on board- - - Hold up, hold up, hold up.
什么警察
What cop?
你在说什么啊
What are you talking about?
听着 我理解沃尔特这种人不认识曼尼
Listen, I get that a guy like Walt doesn't know who Manny is,
但所有人都认识沃尔特
but everybody knows who Walt is.
难道曼尼是个有妄想症的跟踪狂吗
Is Manny a delusional stalker?
不 大概只是嫉妒
Nah, it's probably jealousy.
现在沃尔特的身价 算上球队合同和赞助 已经超过八百万了
Walt's worth over 8 million in NIL deals and sponsorships.
大学男子篮球联赛以前靠着选手们的才华
The NCAA used to make all of the money
赚得盆满钵满的
off the talent of the players, all right?
但是运动员都是学生 他们不能拿钱
But the athletes were students, so they can't get paid.
他们不被允许收取自己努力赚来的钱
They weren't allowed to make money off of their hard work.
直到几年前他们改变了规则
Well, until a few years ago, they changed the rules,
然后学生运动员就可以
and then student athletes could profit
通过个大品牌来盈利
off their personal brands.
现在选手可以用自己的名字 图像
Players are now allowed to make money
还有肖像来赚钱了
off of their name, image, and likeness.
是啊 我之前看到过一篇阿默斯特体操运动员的报道
Yeah, I read an article about a gymnast at Amherst.
她每发一条广告就有五万块进账
She makes, like, $50, 000 off of every sponsored post.
曼尼水平如何
And how good was Manny?
如果他没有受伤 没有被抛弃
If he wasn't injured and he wasn't dropped,
他能不能像沃尔特那么成功
could he be as successful as Walt?
他作为高中球员 是全国排名前50的
As a high school prospect, he ranked amongst the top 50
控球后卫
point guards in the country.
完全可以轻轻松松赚个几百万
He could have made a couple million easy.
怎么了 雷米
What's up, Remy?
他们刚刚在哈姆顿找到了彼得·李 他还活着
They just found Pete Lee alive in Hamden.
急救人员给他检查过 送他回家了
Medics checked him out, and they're taking him home.
-好消息啊  -我在过去路上了
- That's good news. - I'm on my way.
雷和巴恩斯 过去跟我汇合
Ray and Barnes, meet me there.
-好  -好
- Yep. - All right.
我根本不知道他要干什么
I had no idea what he was gonna do.
前一秒他还是个迷路的孩子
One second, he seemed like a lost kid,
后一秒就爆发了
and the next minute, he'd explode.
你还活着真的很幸运了
You're lucky to be alive.
他放你走的时候有说过什么吗
Did he happen to say anything when he let you go?
他让我停车滚下去的时候
When he told me to stop and get out,
我可不会多嘴问为什么
I wasn't gonna ask any questions.
你知道他为什么要劫持你吗
And do you have any idea why he took you?
他整个人都很混乱
Uh, he was all over the place,
一直在问我的机构为什么抛弃了他
asking me why my agency dropped him.
他觉得是因为他没有很快
He figured it was because he didn't get drafted
被NBA选秀挑走
by the NBA fast enough.
所以他才决定出国去打职业
That's why he decided to go pro abroad.
他觉得如果自己在新西兰表现够好
He thought if he did well in New Zealand,
就可以转会回到NBA队伍里
he could transfer back to an NBA team here.
但事实不是这样的吗
Which wasn't the case?
不可能
No way.
他是瑕疵品
He was damaged goods.
所有贿赂丑闻当中涉及的人都是
Everybody named in the bribery scandal was.
什么丑闻
What scandal?
2019年夏天
Summer of 2019,
在曼尼要去中央堪萨斯大学之前
right before Manny was about to go to Central Kansas,
有一个特别行动小组在调查
there was a task force investigating coaches
贿赂球员去选择特定学校的教练
who were bribing prospects to commit to their colleges.
不只是教练 还有赞助商
And not just coaches- - it was also sponsors,
经纪人财务经理等等
agents, financial managers.
很多人因为给优秀球员牵线搭桥而拿到了回扣
A lot of people got kickbacks for hooking up top talent.
高中球员应该是不能和这些人对话的
High school prospects aren't even supposed to talk
也包括经纪人在内
to those folks, including agents.
当时并不是要达成什么协议 只是介绍一下
W- well, no deals were made, just introductions.
那时候规则马上就要改了
The rules were about to change,
大家都看得出来
and everyone saw the writing on the wall.
曼尼和这次丑闻有什么关系
And how was Manny involved with this scandal?
他去中央堪萨斯大学是拿了钱吗
Did he take a bribe for attending CKU?
看上去是的
It looked like it.
他高三的时候
When he was a high school senior,
打比赛掉了一颗牙 不得不去做种牙
he busted a tooth in a game and had to get an implant.
结果发现曼尼在中央堪萨斯大学的教练
It turns out Manny's coach at CKU
替他付了牙科费用
paid that dental bill for him.
这是多少钱
How much are we talking?
不多 四五千吧
Not much, maybe four or five grand.
但贿赂就是贿赂
But a bribe's a bribe.
曼尼直到今天才知道这些事情吗
And Manny didn't know about any of this until today?
他是这么说的
That's what he said.
我记得中央堪萨斯大学悄悄解雇了那个教练
I remember CKU quietly removed that coach
并且撤回了对所有他招募来的球员的邀约
and withdrew their offers to all his recruits.
他们直接无视了那些孩子 就像我们对曼尼所做的一样
They ghosted those kids like we did to Manny.
警方是怎么查到这笔牙科账单的
How did the cops even find out about the dental payment?
中央堪萨斯大学的教练承认了
The coach at Central Kansas copped to it.
他说曼尼的高中教练山姆·内森
He said Manny's high school coach Sam Nathan
打电话给他 让他付这笔钱 当是个人情
called him and asked him to, uh, cover it as a favor.
这件事曼尼也不知道
Manny didn't know about that, either,
我告诉他的时候 他气疯了
and when I told him, he was furious.
-好  -让哈娜和妮娜
·AlI right. - Tell Hana and Nina
尽快赶到内森教练家
to get to Coach Nathan's house as soon as possible.
曼尼 你他妈干什么呢
Manny, what the hell are you doing?
你他妈给我闭嘴
Shut your damn mouth.
曼尼 是我啊
Manny, it's me,
-是教练  -闭嘴
Coach- - - Shut up!
把枪放下
Put the gun down.
彼得·李什么都告诉我了
Pete Lee told me everything.
我不会再听你说话了
I'm done listening to you.
内森教练 我们是联调局的
Coach Nathan, FBI.
有人吗
Hello?
有人在家吗
Anybody home?
没人
Clear!
哈娜 你们发现什么没有
Hana, what do you got?
前门被踹开了
The front door's kicked in.
客厅里一塌糊涂 内森不在这里
The living room's a wreck. Nathan's not here.
我觉得曼尼把他带走了
I think Manny took him.
嗨 雷米
Hey, Remy.
内森教练的车在车库里
Coach Nathan's car is in the garage,
所以我改了全境通告 告知大家嫌犯持有武器
so I'm changing the BOLO to armed, dangerous,
非常危险 并劫持了人质
and with a hostage in tow.
没有血迹 没有弹壳
No blood, no shell casings.
如果教练还活着 那真是个奇迹
If Coach is alive, it's a miracle.
他昨天完全没提这些事吗
He didn't mention any of this yesterday?
他骗我们是有理由的 我们得弄清楚为什么
He lied to us for a reason. We gotta figure out why.
各位 我刚刚搜查了卧室
Guys, I just searched the bedroom,
在教练的床头柜上发现了非常奇怪的东西
and I found the strangest thing in the coach's nightstand.
沃尔特·费尔顿的最新遗嘱
Walt Felton's last will and testament.
沃尔特·费尔顿
Walt Felton?
是的 日期是两个月前的
Yeah, dated from two months ago.
我们找沃尔特谈话的时候 他从来没提过
Walt never said anything about knowing Coach
认识教练啊
when we talked to him.
沃尔特不仅认识教练
Not only does Walt know Coach,
而且这上面还指派教练成为他遗嘱的执行人
it says he made him the executor of his will.
-什么  -如果沃尔特死了
- What? - If Walt were to die,
那么教练就有责任确保所有的钱
Coach would be responsible for making sure all the money
按照遗嘱上的要求分配到人
went to the right people listed in his will.
这案子快把我逼疯了
This case is driving me insane.
我们到底漏掉了什么
What the hell are we missing?
沃尔特到底为什么会给内森教练这么大权利
Why the hell would Walt give Coach Nathan so much power?
这根本说不通
It doesn't make any sense.
不 我们必须得弄清楚他们俩之间的联系
No, we have to find the connection between the two
好 沃尔特是在德州上的高中
So okay, Walt went to high school in Texas.
从圣杰瑞米高中毕业
He graduated from St. Jerome's.
你觉得他之前还读过别的学校吗
What, are you thinking he went somewhere before?
-我不知道 或许吧  -看看这些
- I don't know, maybe. - Let's go through these.
-让我看看  -好
·Let me see. - Okay.
沃尔福德高中
Walford High School
有必要的话给我一页一页看过去
Search every damn page if we have to.
等一下 2019的呢
Wait a second, 2019?
就在这里
I got this one right here.
2019.
等一下 你们看这个
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Look at this.
沃尔特高一的时候
Walt's freshman year.
他在内森教练手下打过球
He played for Coach Nathan.
这位教练很受以前球员的敬爱啊
This coach gets a lot of love from his former players. ②G④曲
有很多贺卡和感谢信
He's got a bunch of cards and thank- you letters.
至少他还有获得爱的途径
Well, at least he's getting it from somewhere
因为没有别人爱他了
because he's not getting it anywhere else.
他用了五个不同的约会网站
He's on five different dating sites.
总得努力一把吧
You gotta shoot your shot somewhere.
他的简介看着也是这个意思
Well, his profile says the same thing.
不抽烟
"No smokers.
想要保持健康生活方式
Interested in maintaining a healthy lifestyle. "
真有意思
That's interesting.
不抽烟 但是有雪茄刀
A non- smoker with a cigar cutter.
-那是个硬盘吗  -是啊
·Is that a hard drive? - Yeah.
好了
Okay.
他为什么会有沃尔特的出生证明
Why does he have Walt's birth certificate?
你知道他是出生在渥太华的吗
You know he was born in Ottawa?
他是加拿大人吗
He's Canadian?
费尔顿在沃尔福德上过学
Felton went to Walford.
或许这就是为什么内森教练
Well, that might explain why Coach Nathan has
藏了一个满是沃尔特个人档案的硬盘
a hidden hard drive filled with Walt's personal documents.
我刚刚发现了他的加拿大出生证明
I just found his Canadian birth certificate.
这儿还有些照片
There are some photos here.
这是他把名字从沃尔特·费尔斯通
This is a petition from when he changed his name
改成沃尔特·费尔顿时的申请书
from Walt Felstone to Walt Felton.
这是领养文件
These are adoption papers. 202 JUME 22
正好是在他改名的时候
Around the same time he legally changed his name,
沃尔特被内森教练收养了
Walt was also adopted by Coach Nathan.
我们只是在干什么 曼尼
What are we doing here, Manny?
我不知道
I don't know.
我只是需要思考
I just need to think.
是啊 你确实需要
Yeah. You do.
但你还是有出路的
There's still a way out of here, though,
如果你愿意投入的话
if you can commit.
我是投入了 然后你耍了我
I did commit, and you screwed me.
就像五年前
Just like you did five years ago
你让中央堪萨斯大学来付我的牙科账单的时候
when you told CKU to pay that dental bill.
我是想帮你
I was trying to help you.
那时候所有人都在付钱给球员
Everyone was paying recruits back then.
是标准操作
It was a standard practice.
你拿到第一份职业合约之后就会还钱的
I told CKU you'd pay them back after your first pro contract.
我从来就没拿到过合同
I never got a contract.
是啊 这能怪谁呢
Yeah, whose fault was that?
你这臭脾气就是忍不住啊
Could never keep your damn cool.
失误一次你就躺平放弃了
One bad play, and you'd roll over and give up.
我一直都相信你能成功的 曼尼
I always believed in you, Manny.
现在也是
And I still do.
我昨天给你发短信叫你不要联系我是有理由的
I texted you yesterday not to contact me for a reason.
我不是要放弃你
I wasn't giving up on you.
我只是不想警察过来 毁了计划
I just didn't want the cops to come along and...ruin the plan.
我们还是可以实现它的
We can still make this happen.
怎么实现
How?
只要他死 我会确保
As long as he ends up dead, I'll see to it
你有足够的钱去墨西哥 古巴
you have enough money to live in Mexico, Cuba,
任何你想去的地方过完下半辈子
wherever you want for the rest of your life.
你只需要听我一次就行了
AlI you gotta do is listen to me for once.
你能做到吗
Can you do that?
沃尔特是被一位非常投入的单亲妈妈养大的
Walt is raised by a devoted single mother
她每次比赛都会去看 从未错过
who never misses a game.
可是四年前她居然在他改名之后
But then she lets Coach Nathan adopt him
让内森教练收养了他
four years ago after he changes his name?
我觉得不是她让他收养的
I don't think she let him.
我觉得是她请他收养的
I think she asked him to.
为什么
Why?
为了钱
Money.
我在看联赛的规则
I'm reading the NIL rules here.
你必须得是美国公民才能够从中获利
You have to be a U. S. citizen to profit off of them.
所以他妈妈让内森教练同意
So his mom gets Coach Nathan to agree...
是啊 教练看到沃尔特打球
Yeah, Coach watches Walt play,
知道他会成为巨星 就觉得等联赛的钱进账
knows he's gonna be a big star, figures he's gonna get
他也能分一杯羹
a piece of the pie when the NIL money starts rolling in.
我查了内森教练的财务状况 没什么异常的
I ran Coach Nathan's financials, and nothing popped.
他一年工资不到五万
I mean, he makes barely 50K a year
生活也没有超出这个水准
and lives within his means.
我知道这都不犯法
I get none of this is illegal,
但是这和他好好男孩的形象是不是背道而驰了
but doesn't this all go against his"good boy"image?
他的公关团队肯定非常努力
I mean, his PR team must work hard
才瞒下了这件事吧
to keep this all a secret.
除非他们不知道
Unless they don't know.
领养文件是加密的
You know, the adoption papers are sealed.
当你搜索沃尔特·费尔顿的时候
And when you search"Walt Felton, "
也不会搜到渥太华的沃尔特·费尔斯通
nothing about Walter Felstone from Ottawa came up.
是 但这都解释不了
Yeah, but none of this explains
曼尼为什么要对教练下手
why Manny is targeting Coach.
他没有
He's not.
目标一直都是沃尔特
Walt was always the target.
你们想想
Think about it.
教练收养沃尔特 是觉得能分到
Coach adopts Walt thinking that he's gonna get
沃尔特的钱 但他没有
some of Walt's riches, and he doesn't.
并且两个月前
Then two months ago,
教练被扇了一个更大的耳光
Coach gets an even bigger slap in the face.
沃尔特直接从遗嘱里排除了他
Walt basically writes him out of his will- -
在教练为了他做了那么多之后
after everything Coach has done for him.
是啊 他肯定很生气吧
Yeah, I'm sure that pissed him off.
但沃尔特指定了教练做他遗嘱的执行人吧
But Walt did make Coach the executor of his will, right?
-是的  -在纽约法律下
Right. - Under New York law,
执行人执行遗嘱 是可以拿到一笔佣金的
the executor gets a commission for overseeing the will.
这笔佣金会是整体资产的百分之几
It's a percentage of the total estate value.
考虑到沃尔特的身价 这可是大钱
And given what Walt is worth, we're talking big- ass money.
是啊 也是要沃尔特死的一大理由
Yeah, that's a big- ass reason to want Walt dead.
这就是曼尼的作用了
That's where Manny comes in.
这教练根本没把选手当是家人
Coach was never about his players being family.
他只是利用 剥削他们 甚至可能嫉妒他们
He uses them, exploits them- - probably even jealous of them.
然后他找上曼尼 操纵了这个可怜孩子
And he goes to Manny and manipulates this poor kid.
他知道他从新西兰回来了
He knew he was back from New Zealand,
受了伤 前途无望 心情抑郁 身无分文
injured, hopeless, depressed, broke.
他找上他说 如果你杀了沃尔特
He goes to him, and he says, if you kill Walt,
我就把遗嘱执行人的佣金分你一部分
I'll give you a cut of the executor's fee to do it.
好 所以他们都觉得
AlI right, so they're both thinking
沃尔特赚到了钱 他们也得分一杯羹
Walt got his, they need to get theirs.
你是说曼尼和教练是串通好的
You're saying that Manny and the coach are working together,
然后演了一出绑架戏码吗
and they staged this kidnapping?
我敢打赌是
I'd bet the damn farm on it.
沃尔特今晚有比赛
Walt has a game tonight.
他正在直播
He's live streaming right now.
托宾国
Tobin Nation!
我们马上要去普罗维登斯了
We're about to hit the road for Providence,
情绪非常高涨
and the mood is hype.
不仅如此 看看谁来送行了
Not only that, look who showed up to send us off,
我最大的粉丝之一
one of my biggest fans.
有什么祝福的话吗 内森教练
What's the good word, Coach Nathan?
我就是来祝你好运
I just came by to wish you luck.
我还记得你第一次对着那大块头
I remember the first time I saw you tomahawk dunk
-战斧式灌篮 我就知道  -把手机放下
over that big man, I knew- - Drop the phone.
把手机放下
Drop the phone!
-你们俩跟我走  -别动
You two are coming with me. - Hey, don't movel
-别动  -把枪放下
Don't movel- Drop the gun!
-放下  -放下 不然我打死他
Drop it. - Drop it, or I'll shoot him.
过去 都给我过去
Come around. Come around.
曼尼拿着枪 但发号施令的是教练
Manny's holding the gun, but Coach is calling the shots.
他不知道我们已经查到他了
He doesn't know we're on to him.
这是计划的一部分 但直播不是
This was part of the plan, but the live stream wasn't.
他是在假装被曼尼劫持
He's pretending to be Manny's hostage
好让沃尔特和他们独处 然后杀了他
so they can get Walt alone and kill him.
是啊 然后他们大概就要翻脸了
Yeah, then they'll probably turn on each other.
教练现在还不知道我们已经知道他是幕后黑手了
As far as Coach knows, we still think he's the victim.
那我们就反过来耍他一把
Let's play him like a fiddle.
救 救命 他突然跑来我家
He- help! He showed up in my house!
退后 退后 手抱头
Get back, get back! Hands on your head!
曼尼 我是联调局特别探员雷米·斯科特
Manny, I'm Special Agent Remy Scott of the FBI.
我需要请你喘口气
I need you to take a breath
然后慢下来 孩子
and slow everything way down, son.
只要沃尔特不走 就不会有人受伤
As long as Walt stays, nobody gets hurt.
那我们就先把其他人放走
Let's start by letting everyone else go.
只能放走车上的人
Only the guys on the bus.
其他人都留下 懂了吗
Everyone else stays. All right?
没问题 雷
You got it. Ray.
快点 走 下车
Come on. Go. Off the bus.
走 快走
Go. Come on. Let's go.
听我说 曼尼
Listen to me, Manny.
你人生中所有
All the adults in your life
本该帮你控制压力的成年人
who were supposed to help you handle the pressure,
都让你失望了
they let you down instead.
我们都是一家人 教练
We're all family here, Coach.
不如你给曼尼解释一下 为什么警方去调查
Why don't you tell Manny what you were so worried about
对中央堪萨斯大学的贿赂时 你会那么紧张吧
when the cops came sniffing around about that bribe to CKU?
你 你说什么呢
Wh- what the hell are you talking about?
沃尔特是加拿大人
Walt's from Canada.
教练走法律途径收养了他
Coach legally adopted him
好让他成为美国公民
so he could become a U S. citizen
so he could become a U. S. citizen
去赚那些姓名 肖像权的钱
and make all that name, image, and likeness money.
然后你和曼尼要找个沃尔特落单的时候
And you and Manny were gonna get Walt alone.
再杀了他
And then you were gonna kill him.
然后你准备再对曼尼反水
And you were gonna turn the tables on Manny
把他也杀了 对吧 教练
and murder him, right, Coach?
你觉得我们会相信你 是吧
And we'd believe you, right?
可怜的内森教练 只是在面对一个被通缉的杀手时
Poor Coach Nathan just defending himself
选择了自保
against a wanted killer.
你没想到我们会查出来 你是他们的教练
You didn't think we'd figure out you're their coach.
那又如何
So what?
为更少的钱做更糟的事的人也不是没有
People have done worse for less.
这孩子是我挖掘出来的
I discovered the kid.
是我让他走上了出名和赚钱的道路
I put him on the path of fame and fortune.
我不配分一杯羹吗
I don't deserve a piece of the pie?
而你 你的一切都是我给的
And you, you owe me everything.
而你却把我从遗嘱中排除
Instead you cut me out of your will
把我指定成了执行人
and make me your damn executor.
我相信了你
I trusted you.
比起我爸 我更相信你
I trusted you more than my pops!
你说我到NBA是我们的目标
You said it was our goal for me to make it to the NBA!
那确实是我们的目标
It was our goal.
你们这群被宠坏的小鬼却从未给我过什么
And you spoiled brats would never give me my due.
我为你们牺牲了那么多
And for all the sacrifices I've made for you- -
为了所有的球员
for all my players.
你们觉得比赛之后说两句感谢
What, do you- - you think postgame shout- outs and- -
寄几张明信片就能付清账单了吗
and postcards pay the bills?
因为你 我的人生完了 教练
Because of you, my life is over, Coach
热知识
Here's a news flash.
你的膝盖受伤的时候你的人生就已经完了
Your life was over when your knee blew out.
是啊 确实是完了
Yeah, it's over,
但那是因为我自己 就那一次
but on my terms for once.
走 走啊
Let's go. Let's go!
把枪放下 孩子
Put the gun down, son.
把枪放下
Put it down.
不 不要
Hey, hey, hey! No! S DOT
叫救护车
Call an ambulance.
好 谢谢
Okay, thanks
教练没挺过来 曼尼也要去坐牢了
Coach didn't make it, and Manny's on his way to jail.
但沃尔特这孩子太可怜了
I feel so bad for this kid Walt, though.
他还有份两百万的卖鞋合同
Well, he has a $2 million shoe contract.
他应该会没事的
Maybe he'll be okay.
我不理解
I don't get that.
我们教这些孩子
I mean, we tell these kids,
去赢 去拿冠军 然后在他们拿到之后
go get the brass ring, and then they do,
又中伤他们 让这个系统对他们为所欲为
and we vilify them and let the system screw them over.
这根本讲不通
It just makes no sense.
是啊 应该把他们挣到的东西给他们吧
Yeah, let them get what they earn, right?
是啊
Yeah.
但确实挺糟糕的 他的领养秘密曝光了
Sucks, though. His adoption secret is out now.
所有人都乐于原谅明星和运动员
We love to forgive our stars and athletes,
他可是明星运动员
and he's both.
你怎么样了 你还好吗
Hey, how you doing? You okay?
我没事
Yeah, I'm okay.
就是夏洛特那边不太好
Just having a hard time with Charlotte.
她不回我短信
She's not replying to my texts.
我知道这种感觉
I know the feeling.
你觉得费尔韦瑟医生怎么样
What'd you think of Dr. Fairweather?
你们去见过她了吗
You guys get to go see her yet?
我们去了一次 抱歉 她真的很好
Yeah, we had a session. I'm sorry, she was great.
谢谢你
Thank you.
但这真的很难 你懂吧
It's just been hard, you know?
真的太难了
It's been really hard.
是啊
Yeah.
如果你需要找人聊聊的话 随时可以找我
If you ever need to talk, I'm here.
谢谢
Thanks.
雷米
Hey, Remy.
要去喝一杯吗
You want to grab a drink?
我现在不太想回家
I don't really feel like going home right now.
我很乐意
I'd love to.
我们都愿意去参加治疗
We're both willing to do the therapy,
所以显然我们都还是想挽救这段婚姻的
so we're obviously both still in it.
这就是我现在
Mm. - That's what I'm trying
努力想要抓住的
to hang onto right now.
听我的 虽然费尔韦瑟医生
Well, take it from me, as excellent
非常优秀 但还是需要时间的
as Dr. Fairweather is, it's still gonna take time.
-是啊  -而且根据我的记录
- Yeah. - And given my track record,
我觉得你应该不会想听我关于婚姻的建议
I don't think you want marriage advice from me.
那确实
That is true.
我觉得应该和我们团队合作这么优秀
I imagine it's not too different from what makes
所需要的东西差不太多吧 你懂的
our team work so damn well together, you know,
良好的交流 坦诚 知道自己的弱点
good communication, honesty, knowing your weaknesses,
提供自己的长处
bringing your strengths to the table.
仅此而已
- That's all it is. - Hmm.
听着 我知道家庭关系能有多棘手
Look, I know how tough family can be.
我侄子科瑞现在在跟我一起住
My nephew Corey has been staying with me and- -
我就是不明白
Ijust don't get it.
这傻孩子差一点就能从医学院毕业了
I mean, this dumbass kid was this close
结果他就这么退学了
to graduating med school, and he just drops out.
他是退学了 还是只是花点时间
He drops out, or he just takes some time off
休息一下呢
to get a little break?
我觉得他自己都不知道
I don't think he even knows.
如果他自己有计划 或许我可以放心让他自己想通
I might trust him to figure things out if he had a plan,
但我早上去上班的时候 他还在睡觉
but when I leave in the morning for work, he's still sleeping.
我晚上回家的时候 天知道他在哪里
When I come home at night, he's out God knows where.
-是啊  -我叫他去找份兼职
Yeah. - I told him to get
但他不听
a part time job, but he doesn't listen.
我想让他的生活有点安排
Try to give him some structure.
他都快把我逼疯了
He's driving me nuts.
我也不知道他为什么不把脏袜子
And I don't know why he doesn't put his dirty socks
放进洗衣篓里
in the hamper.
-如果这就是为人父母  -是啊
- If this is parenting...- Oh, yeah.
糟透了
Sucks.
你为什么不直接跟他坦白说清楚呢
Well, why don't you just be honest with him?
告诉他你是什么感受
Tell him how you feel,
无论是好的 还是困难的
about the good stuff and the hard stuff.
然后努力记住你们的共同点
Then maybe try to remember what you both have in common...
小迈
Mikey.
-是啊  -再来一杯吗
Yeah. - Another round?
好 拿份菜单来吧
Yeah. How about a couple of menus?
我饿死了
I'm starving.
你不介意在酒吧吃饭吧
You okay with eating at the bar?
开什么玩笑 我最爱了
You kidding me? It's my favorite.
我也是
Me too.
干杯
Cheers.